[{"answer": "Chris, I'm losing you because we've just had a major, major intensification of this storm.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Ali, what is the situation now?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "It feels like all of these three feet are falling on us right now, Chris, as we speak.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "They could get up to three feet, right?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Absolutely, it's under a state of emergency.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Poppy, what is the current condition?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Poppy, thank you very much.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Nothing like anchoring your first show in a blizzard, right?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "In fact, it's already happened, Chris.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Ashleigh, what's the latest?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "One low pressure center, Chris, brought the cold.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Help us give us a sense of why this blizzard is a concoction of these two fronts, what it means and where it's moving?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I'm a little worried about they say coastal flooding right now, but the mayor, he said, no, it's only going to be two feet.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "How are you managing right now?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "In a matter of a week.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "When did you expect to move back in?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Very concerned right now, but so far, it looks good.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Yes, about six hours ago, even before the snow started coming down, Chris, we were told that 800 customers were without power.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Anybody coming out saying they lost power, or so far so good?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Some guns.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "What do we know?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Well, in many ways, this is -- this is going to be a traditional fugitive hunt.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "How will that play into how they strategize in this manhunt?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Well, this case obviously is getting national media attention.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "How does that play into making this a difficult task for Mr. Dorner, hopefully?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "WECKER: It is a fair assessment.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Isn't that a fair assessment?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "There's absolutely no basis in reality for his complaints that he was mistreated, that there was any kind of police corruption.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Is there anything in there that fuels this sense of revenge that Dorner says he has?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes, I did read about that.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Do you know anything about that?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "We do know that he's paranoid.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "So how do we catch him?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Can you hear us?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Current situation is we have blowing snow and heavy snow coming in Boston now.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "What is the current situation for you there?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "We have a 24 hour service at city hall, 635-4500.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "What has the response been like?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Well, it's obviously a very serious storm.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "On the phone with us, Mr. Mayor, what is the latest for you?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "You know, I just finished the command staff update, and we have no power outages whatsoever.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "What reports are you getting so far?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Look, I'm really proud of the state of New Jersey as a whole.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Coming out of sandy, to the extent there is any silver lining, what did you learn there that helped prepare for this one?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Well, I lost a lot of stuff in my house.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "What are you recovering from already?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Well, everybody has fear, you know.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Is everybody OK so far?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "All the best in the recovery out there, OK?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Yes, Chris.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "I got you on the phone, pastor?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "I'm doing well, thank God.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "How are you doing this evening?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "Everybody is really nervous.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Let me ask you, how is everybody dealing with the anticipation of what may come with this blizzard?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Some people did evacuate.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Have people left in preparation for this storm or is everybody still there?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "The things we need right now are mostly proteins and food.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "What do you need?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Chris, it's about halftime.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "What do we know now?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Chad, thank you so much for that.", "docId": "130208pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Chris?", "qSentId": 684}]